http://www.iewc.com/privacy-policy

Submit
Forget your username/password?
Don't have an account yet?
Register
Cart
(0)
Search Jobs
Why Work at IEWC?
About IEWC
IEWC advances the way the world connects, stays powered, and drives forward through comprehensive supply chain and logistics solutions for wire, cable, and wire management products. For more than 55 years, IEWC has been an entrusted partner for thousands of companies in manufacturing, infrastructure, broadcast, professional audio-visual and telecommunications. An employee-owned company in USA, IEWC has 30 locations in 11 countries, serving customers in 96 countries.
Learn More
Resources
Literature
Catalogs & Linecards
Color Code Guide
Conflict Materials
View All
Product Resources
Optimize the Lifespan of Your High-Flex Cables
Anatomy of Vinyl Electrical Tape
How to Choose the Optimal Wire Labeling Solution
Alternatives to 200°C UL/CSA FEP Wires
Technical Guide
Educational Resources
What Every Purchaser Needs to Know About Sourcing Wire & Cable
Voltage Drop: Picking the Right Cable for the Long Run
Wire & Cables 101 for Purchasing and Sales Professionals
Wire & Cable 102 for Purchasing and Sales Professionals
Glossary of Terms
Business Resources
Logistics Central
Tariff Central
Weather Central
Covid-19 Central
News & Events
News
Tradeshows
Press Releases
IEWC Ranked Number 46 Most Successful Private Company on Deloitte's 2020 Wisconsin 75
November 19, 2020
IEWC Named a 2020 ‘Best Place to Work in Milwaukee’ by Milwaukee Business Journal
October 29, 2020
Helping You Deliver Essential Solutions During COVID-19
March 23, 2020
How Vibration, Noise and Crosstalk can Cause Downtime
November 19, 2019
Evolution of ISO High Voltage Copper Cable Standards for Vehicles
November 13, 2019
Commercial vs. Industrial Cables: 9 Essential Tests
July 15, 2019
View All News
View All Tradeshows
IEWC Announces Pat Rislov as Chief Supply Chain Officer
November 19, 2020
IEWC Announces Acquisition of Jupiter Communications
November 10, 2020
IEWC Fully Integrates European Divisions as Premier Cables
October 1, 2020
IEWC Announces New Distribution Center in Hermosillo, Sonora, México
August 1, 2019
IEWC Announces Tim Teske as New Chief Financial Officer
May 7, 2019
IEWC Increases Support of Electric Vehicle and Rail/Transit Markets with HUBER+SUHNER Partnership
April 22, 2019
View All Press Releases
Newsletters
Hot Wire
Auto Industry Outlook for 2021
December 10, 2020
View All
Connection
Electric & Hybrid Vehicle Solutions
September 26, 2019
View All
Cart
(0)
PRODUCTS & SERVICES
Wire & Cable
Aerospace & Defense Wire & Cable
Lead Wire
Multi-Conductor Cable
Coaxial Cable
View All
Automotive Wire & Cable
Search Jobs
Why Work at IEWC?
Code of Ethics
The Environment
Certification & Compliances
Industries We Serve
About IEWC
IEWC advances the way the world connects, stays powered, and drives forward through comprehensive supply chain and logistics solutions for wire, cable, and wire management products. For more than 55 years, IEWC has been an entrusted partner for thousands of companies in manufacturing, infrastructure, broadcast, professional audio-visual and telecommunications. An employee-owned company in USA, IEWC has 30 locations in 11 countries, serving customers in 96 countries.
Learn More
Resources
Literature
Catalogs & Linecards
Color Code Guide
Conflict Materials
View All
Product Resources
Optimize the Lifespan of Your High-Flex Cables
Anatomy of Vinyl Electrical Tape
How to Choose the Optimal Wire Labeling Solution
Alternatives to 200°C UL/CSA FEP Wires
Technical Guide
Educational Resources
What Every Purchaser Needs to Know About Sourcing Wire & Cable
Voltage Drop: Picking the Right Cable for the Long Run
Wire & Cables 101 for Purchasing and Sales Professionals
Wire & Cable 102 for Purchasing and Sales Professionals
Glossary of Terms
Business Resources
Logistics Central
Tariff Central
Weather Central
Covid-19 Central
News & Events
News
IEWC Ranked Number 46 Most Successful Private Company on Deloitte's 2020 Wisconsin 75
November 19, 2020
IEWC Named a 2020 ‘Best Place to Work in Milwaukee’ by Milwaukee Business Journal
October 29, 2020
Helping You Deliver Essential Solutions During COVID-19
March 23, 2020
How Vibration, Noise and Crosstalk can Cause Downtime
November 19, 2019
Evolution of ISO High Voltage Copper Cable Standards for Vehicles
November 13, 2019
Commercial vs. Industrial Cables: 9 Essential Tests
July 15, 2019
View All News
Tradeshows
View All Tradeshows
Press Releases
IEWC Announces Pat Rislov as Chief Supply Chain Officer
November 19, 2020
IEWC Announces Acquisition of Jupiter Communications
November 10, 2020
IEWC Fully Integrates European Divisions as Premier Cables
October 1, 2020
IEWC Announces New Distribution Center in Hermosillo, Sonora, México
August 1, 2019
IEWC Announces Tim Teske as New Chief Financial Officer
May 7, 2019
IEWC Increases Support of Electric Vehicle and Rail/Transit Markets with HUBER+SUHNER Partnership
April 22, 2019
View All Press Releases
Newsletters
Hot Wire
Auto Industry Outlook for 2021
December 10, 2020
View All
Connection
Submit
Forget your username/password?
Don't have an account yet?
Register
Call Us
(877) 613-4392
Contact Us
IEWC: Wire, Cable & Wire...
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
1.1. What is your personal data?
Personal data is information that can identify you as an individual.
1.2. How do we process your personal data?
IEWC complies with mandates to keep your personal data up to date; by storing and destroying it securely; by not collecting or retaining more data than is necessary; by protecting your personal data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, and disclosure; and by ensuring that we take appropriate action to protect your personal data.We use your personal data to:
Manage IEWC.com and deliver the products and services that individuals have requested.
Inform you of products or services we offer.
Sell, process, and deliver our product or service orders.
Provide access to credit terms when requested.
Contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinions of current products and services or of potential new services that we may offer.
Comply with our legal obligations.
Protect the interests of an individual or a group of individuals.
Carry out a task in the public interest, such as a request for national security purposes.
Process data related to employment, social security, or protection laws of employees or those looking for a job at IEWC.
Comply with court orders or defend you and/or IEWC in court if necessary.
1.3. Sharing your personal data
Your personal data will be treated as strictly confidential and we will only share it with IEWC employees, our shipping and delivery vendors, and our service providers. We will share your data with third parties outside of IEWC only if you give us permission. We intend to ask for your permission specifically in context of you requesting information, purchasing a product or service, registering on our website for a better online experience, or for applying with us for a job.
1.4. How long do we keep your personal data?
We only keep your personal data for as long as it is needed from a business perspective or where accounting, employment, and legal commitments dictate.
1.5. Your rights and your personal data
You have the following rights that we will respect:
The right to request a copy of any personal data that IEWC holds about you;
The right to request that IEWC correct any personal data if it is found to be wrong;
The right to request your personal data be erased when it is no longer necessary for IEWC to retain such data;
The right to withdraw your consent to IEWC’s use of your information;
The right to request that IEWC provide you with your personal data in electronic format;
The right to ask IEWC to stop using your data until any dispute around data accuracy is resolved; and
Additional information on your personal rights can be obtained from the German Data Protection Authority (DPA), the UK’s Information Commissioner’s Office or the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC).
1.6. Further use of your data
If we want to use your personal data for any other notice, IEWC will first contact you with an updated notice.
1.7. Contact Details
To exercise your rights under this notice, or for any questions, please contact IEWC’s Marketing Communications Manager.
Password Recovery
Please enter your login email address. We will email instructions for updating your password.
Email
Submit
Success! Instructions for resetting your password have been sent to your email.
OK
